Contacts

- <u>© 4</u>69-237-6035
- mikemojeks@gmail.com
- 100 Tupiter Rd, #2105, Allen TX, 75002
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/kene-mojekwu-4647a5225/
- # https://kenemoj.github.io/website/
- https://github.com/kenemoj

Skills

- C++
- Java
- Python
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- MySQL
- Multitasking
- Go
- · Problem Solving
- Unix/Linux
- PHP
- · Problem Solving
- Analytical Skills
- Microsoft Office

Language

- English
- French(Beginner)
- Igbo

Kene Mojekwu

Computer Science Junior

Computer Science junior at The University of Texas at Arlington working parttime as a student web developer and loves problem solving. Experienced in front-end and back-end development, familiar with programming languages such as JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, Java, Python, C++ among others. Excellent communication skills as wells as great when working in a group.

Education

• BS in Computer Science

The University of Texas at Arlington - Arlington, TX

August 2022 - May 2024

3.1/4.0 GPA

Relevant Coursework: Data Structures and Algorithms, Discrete Structures, Operating Systems

Involvement: National Society of Black Engineers, African Student Organization

AS in Computer Science

Collin County Community College - Plano, TX

August 2022 - May 2024

Relevant Coursework: Programming Fundamentals(I, II, III), Computer Organization Involvement: African Student Organization(Vice-President), Computer Science and Engineering Club

Experience

Student Web Developer (Part-Time)

The University of Texas at Arlington

September 2022 - Present

- Designing and developing web applications that help streamline department operations
- Carrying out interface design and implementation
- Loading and maintaining data used in department applications.
- Carrying out projects while working in a team environment.

Student Assistant - Computer Lab (Part-Time)

Collin County Community College

August 2021 - May 2022

- Assisted all students using the computer lab with specific program instructions, internet access, and lab assignments.
- Performed troubleshooting operations on the computer systems when needed
- Performed regular software backups.
- Conducted regular maintenance on the computers in the lab.

Projects

Course

Created a website for student information exchange. The purpose of the
website was to allow students to communicate amongst themselves as well as
carrying out trades. The design and UI were created using JavaScript, HTML
and CSS while the database was created using MySQL.

Personal

 Created a website containing details about myself. The purpose of the site is to allow the user view details about me and my life and my work. Made using JavaScript, HTML and CSS.